[
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Dominica is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Slovenia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Croatia", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Albania", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Tunisia", 
      "Germany", 
      "North Macedonia", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Andorra"
    ], 
    "question": "Italy shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Austria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Croatia", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Romania", 
      "Poland"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country borders Italy, Switzerland, Germany, Czech Republic, Hungary, Slovenia, and Liechtenstein?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Brussels-Capital Region", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brussels", 
      "Antwerp", 
      "Ghent", 
      "Li\u00e8ge", 
      "Bruges", 
      "Leuven", 
      "Mechelen", 
      "Schaerbeek", 
      "Anderlecht", 
      "Namur"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Province of Brabant?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Togo is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mauritania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Spain", 
      "Andorra", 
      "Portugal", 
      "Malta", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Italy", 
      "France", 
      "Benin", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Togo", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Nigeria"
    ], 
    "question": "Algeria shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Florida", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kansas", 
      "Texas", 
      "California"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American state's name is Spanish for \"flowered\" or \"flowery land\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Federated States of Micronesia is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Guinea", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Guinea-Bissau", 
      "The Gambia", 
      "Senegal", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Togo", 
      "Mali", 
      "Benin", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Cape Verde", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Niger", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Algeria"
    ], 
    "question": "Liberia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Africa", 
      "South America", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "In which continent would you find the Yellow river?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Shimonoseki", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Katsuyama' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Saint Lucia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Palau", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brunei", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Laos", 
      "East Timor", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Thailand", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Japan", 
      "North Korea", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Papua New Guinea", 
      "People's Republic of China", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Federated States of Micronesia", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "Mongolia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Philippines?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Venice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rome", 
      "Milan", 
      "Naples", 
      "Florence", 
      "Turin", 
      "Genoa", 
      "Bologna", 
      "Palermo"
    ], 
    "question": "In which city is the Bridge of Sighs?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kajaani", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Vuolijoki?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Grenada?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Colombia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Chile", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Barbados", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines", 
      "Saint Lucia", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Panama"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Brazil?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Brussels", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Antwerp", 
      "Ghent", 
      "Li\u00e8ge", 
      "Bruges", 
      "Leuven", 
      "Mechelen", 
      "Schaerbeek", 
      "Brussels-Capital Region"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Belgium?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hachi\u014dji", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Yugi' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Turkmenistan is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Namibia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lesotho", 
      "Eswatini", 
      "Angola", 
      "Mozambique", 
      "Malawi", 
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
      "Tanzania", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Comoros", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Madagascar", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Kenya", 
      "Equatorial Guinea"
    ], 
    "question": "Botswana shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Luanda", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brazzaville", 
      "Nairobi", 
      "Dakar"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Angola?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Matsumoto", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Satoyamabe' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Barbados?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Austria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Monaco", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Belgium", 
      "Kingdom of the Netherlands", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Andorra", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Denmark", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Poland", 
      "Slovakia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Switzerland?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pacific Ocean", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Indian Ocean", 
      "Atlantic Ocean", 
      "Mediterranean Sea"
    ], 
    "question": "The Philippines is an archipelago of 7,107 islands in the ________________", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kaliningrad", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Moscow", 
      "Saint Petersburg", 
      "Kazan", 
      "Yekaterinburg", 
      "Ufa", 
      "Rostov-on-Don", 
      "Nizhny Novgorod", 
      "Novosibirsk", 
      "Saratov", 
      "Voronezh"
    ], 
    "question": "'K\u00f6nigsberg' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Lesotho is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Montenegro", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Bulgaria", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Romania", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Malta", 
      "Italy", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Austria", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Moldova", 
      "Poland", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Tunisia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Albania?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Devon\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sussex", 
      "Cornwall", 
      "Dorset"
    ], 
    "question": "In which English county is Dartmoor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "N\u00eemes", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paris", 
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Lyon", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Toulouse", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes"
    ], 
    "question": "'Nemausus' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Maldives?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Philippines", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Papua New Guinea", 
      "East Timor", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Japan", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Solomon Islands", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Laos", 
      "Nauru", 
      "North Korea", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Australia", 
      "Marshall Islands", 
      "Kiribati"
    ], 
    "question": "Palau shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rhode Island\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hawaii", 
      "Maine", 
      "Vermont"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Is The Smallest State In The USA? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ichikawa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Gy\u014dtoku?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Nauru?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tanzania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Malawi", 
      "Kenya", 
      "Mauritius", 
      "Zimbabwe", 
      "Zambia", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Somalia", 
      "Eswatini", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
      "Botswana", 
      "Lesotho", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Djibouti"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Comoros?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Antarctica", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "______________ is the only continent without reptiles or snakes", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Alavus", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'T\u00f6ys\u00e4' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Saint Kitts and Nevis is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Togo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ghana", 
      "Ivory Coast", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Mali", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Liberia", 
      "Guinea", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Sierra Leone", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Senegal", 
      "Guinea-Bissau", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "The Gambia", 
      "Chad"
    ], 
    "question": "Benin shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "El salvador", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Honduras", 
      "Guatemala", 
      "Belize", 
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Panama"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the only Central American country without an Atlantic coastline.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Vaasa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'V\u00e4h\u00e4kyr\u00f6' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Nauru is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rwanda", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gabon", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Malawi", 
      "Kenya", 
      "Zimbabwe", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Chad", 
      "Botswana", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "Mozambique"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Democratic Republic of the Congo?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Greenland\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "New Guinea", 
      "Iceland", 
      "Madagascar"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the largest island in the world.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Okayama", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Makiishi?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Comoros?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Guatemala", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "El Salvador", 
      "Honduras", 
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Cuba", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Panama", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Dominican Republic", 
      "Canada", 
      "Colombia", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Dominica"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Mexico?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Russia\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Austria", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Norway"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Country Is Europe's Highest Mountain Mt Elbrus?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Okazaki", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Mishima?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Belize is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Honduras", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "El Salvador", 
      "Belize", 
      "Guatemala", 
      "Panama", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Cuba", 
      "Haiti", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Dominican Republic", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "Mexico", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines"
    ], 
    "question": "Nicaragua shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Venice\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rome", 
      "Beijing", 
      "Ulaanbaatar"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which City Is Marco Polo Airport?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Istanbul", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ankara", 
      "\u0130zmir", 
      "Bursa", 
      "Edirne", 
      "Trabzon", 
      "Adana", 
      "Sivas", 
      "Antalya", 
      "Konya", 
      "Kayseri"
    ], 
    "question": "'Constantinople' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Tuvalu is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Palau", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brunei", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Laos", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "People's Republic of China", 
      "Japan", 
      "Federated States of Micronesia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Indonesia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Israel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jordan", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Syria", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Turkey", 
      "Iraq", 
      "Saudi Arabia"
    ], 
    "question": "____________ is one_quarter the size of the state of Maine.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ichinomiya", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Oku?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Lesotho?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sudan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South Sudan", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Benin", 
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
      "Eritrea", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Togo", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Tunisia", 
      "Malta"
    ], 
    "question": "Chad shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Danish", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Russian", 
      "British", 
      "Portuguese"
    ], 
    "question": "What Nationality Was The First European To Sail Through The Bering Strait?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Brunswick", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Berlin", 
      "Munich", 
      "Hamburg", 
      "Leipzig", 
      "Dresden", 
      "Nuremberg", 
      "Hanover", 
      "Stuttgart", 
      "Cologne", 
      "Frankfurt am Main"
    ], 
    "question": "'Braunschweig' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Andorra is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sudan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yemen", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Saudi Arabia", 
      "Tanzania", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Central African Republic", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
      "Seychelles", 
      "Oman", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Egypt"
    ], 
    "question": "Ethiopia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lebanon", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jordan", 
      "Israel", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Syria", 
      "Turkey", 
      "Iraq", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Armenia"
    ], 
    "question": "___________ is the only country in the Middle East that does not have a desert.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Shanghai", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hong Kong", 
      "Beijing", 
      "Guangzhou", 
      "Chongqing", 
      "Tianjin", 
      "Suzhou", 
      "Nanjing", 
      "Chengdu", 
      "Harbin", 
      "Wuhan"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Shanqhae?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Togo is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Argentina", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paraguay", 
      "Chile", 
      "Bolivia", 
      "Peru", 
      "Suriname", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Guyana", 
      "Colombia", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Barbados", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines", 
      "Saint Lucia", 
      "Panama", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis"
    ], 
    "question": "Uruguay shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Niagara falls", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lake Huron", 
      "Yosemite", 
      "Appalachian Mountains"
    ], 
    "question": "Which site in North America was named after the Mohawk Indian word meaning \"thunder of waters\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kitaky\u016bsh\u016b", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Tobata' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Togo is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Saudi Arabia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lebanon", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Israel", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "Georgia", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Qatar", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Turkmenistan", 
      "Eritrea", 
      "Yemen", 
      "Oman"
    ], 
    "question": "Iraq shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Reykjavik", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Oslo", 
      "Copenhagen"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Iceland?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ichinomiya", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Oku' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Malaysia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brunei", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Laos", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "People's Republic of China", 
      "Japan", 
      "Federated States of Micronesia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Indonesia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jerusalem", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paris", 
      "Rome", 
      "Istanbul"
    ], 
    "question": "The \"Old City\" of this location is divided into four quarters \u2014 a Christian quarter, a Muslim Quarter, a Jewish Quarter, and an Armenian Quarter.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Maebashi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Haga' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Kiribati is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Argentina", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Chile", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Barbados", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines", 
      "Saint Lucia", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Panama"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Brazil?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "China", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Greece", 
      "Britain", 
      "The USA"
    ], 
    "question": "In which country was natural gas first used as a form of energy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lugano", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Z\u00fcrich", 
      "Bern", 
      "Geneva", 
      "Basel", 
      "Lausanne", 
      "Winterthur", 
      "Lucerne", 
      "St. Gallen", 
      "Fribourg", 
      "Neuch\u00e2tel"
    ], 
    "question": "'Br\u00e8-Aldesago' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "South Korea", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "North Korea", 
      "Palau", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Mongolia", 
      "Federated States of Micronesia", 
      "Laos", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Papua New Guinea", 
      "Marshall Islands", 
      "East Timor", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "Singapore"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Japan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mali\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mauritania", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Nigeria"
    ], 
    "question": "The Town Of Timbuktu Is In Which African Country?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pieks\u00e4m\u00e4ki", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Pieks\u00e4nmaa' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "East Timor is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "People's Republic of China", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Laos", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Pakistan", 
      "Kyrgyzstan", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Tajikistan", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Mongolia", 
      "Afghanistan", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Maldives", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Kazakhstan"
    ], 
    "question": "Bhutan shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oahu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kauai", 
      "Hawaii", 
      "Maui"
    ], 
    "question": "On what island is Pearl Harbour?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Qingdao", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hong Kong", 
      "Beijing", 
      "Shanghai", 
      "Guangzhou", 
      "Chongqing", 
      "Tianjin", 
      "Suzhou", 
      "Nanjing", 
      "Chengdu", 
      "Harbin"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Tsingtao?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Trinidad and Tobago is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "New Zealand", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Solomon Islands", 
      "Vanuatu", 
      "Palau", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Nauru", 
      "Federated States of Micronesia", 
      "Fiji", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Tuvalu", 
      "Kiribati", 
      "Marshall Islands", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Thailand"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Australia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Devon\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sussex", 
      "Cornwall", 
      "Dorset"
    ], 
    "question": "In which English county is Dartmoor?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sasebo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Sakihario' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Comoros is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Republic of the Congo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Botswana", 
      "Zimbabwe", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Malawi", 
      "South Africa", 
      "Tanzania", 
      "Mozambique", 
      "Central African Republic", 
      "Eswatini", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Lesotho"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Angola?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dominican Republic", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Haiti", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Cuba", 
      "Saint Lucia"
    ], 
    "question": "What country is Santo Domingo the capital of?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hamina", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Vehkalahti' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of San Marino?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Slovakia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Croatia", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Poland", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Denmark", 
      "Albania", 
      "Belgium", 
      "North Macedonia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Austria?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Thailand", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cambodia", 
      "Laos", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Brunei"
    ], 
    "question": "____________ means \"land of the free.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aix-en-Provence", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paris", 
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Lyon", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Toulouse", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Aquae Sextiae?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Russia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Estonia", 
      "Latvia", 
      "Lithuania", 
      "Belarus", 
      "Poland", 
      "Ukraine", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Moldova", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Romania", 
      "Denmark", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Austria", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Germany", 
      "Bulgaria", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Finland?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Belgium", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Kingdom of the Netherlands", 
      "France", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Germany", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Denmark"
    ], 
    "question": "Brussels is the capital of which country", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Raahe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Pattijoki?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Tuvalu is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Syria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lebanon", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Turkey", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Georgia", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Greece", 
      "Eritrea", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Bulgaria", 
      "Iran", 
      "Sudan", 
      "Moldova"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Jordan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kuwait City", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Abu Dhabi", 
      "Doha", 
      "Amman"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Kuwait?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kakogawa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Shikata?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of The Gambia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nigeria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Benin", 
      "Niger", 
      "Togo", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Ivory Coast", 
      "Mali", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Angola", 
      "Libya", 
      "Burundi"
    ], 
    "question": "Cameroon shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Africa", 
      "North America", 
      "South America", 
      "Europe"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Of The World's Continents Has The Highest Population? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Toyama", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Hariwara' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Dominica is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Venezuela", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jamaica", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Cuba", 
      "Saint Lucia", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Barbados", 
      "Panama", 
      "Colombia", 
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Guyana", 
      "Honduras", 
      "Belize"
    ], 
    "question": "Dominican Republic shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Buenos Aires", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sao Paolo", 
      "Cordoba", 
      "Santiago"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the capital of Argentina.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "York", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "London", 
      "Cardiff", 
      "Edinburgh", 
      "Glasgow", 
      "Aberdeen", 
      "Liverpool", 
      "Birmingham", 
      "Manchester", 
      "Oxford", 
      "Belfast"
    ], 
    "question": "'Eboracum' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kenya", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yemen", 
      "Eritrea", 
      "Seychelles", 
      "Uganda", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Tanzania", 
      "Sudan", 
      "Saudi Arabia", 
      "Oman", 
      "Comoros", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Qatar", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Malawi", 
      "Kuwait"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Somalia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Denver", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Chicago", 
      "Philadelphia", 
      "San Francisco", 
      "Boston", 
      "New Orleans"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Colorado? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fuji", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Takaoka' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Dominica is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Colombia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Honduras", 
      "El Salvador", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Belize", 
      "Guatemala", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "Cuba", 
      "Dominican Republic", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Peru", 
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Saint Lucia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Panama?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aluminium", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oxygen", 
      "Silicon", 
      "Iron"
    ], 
    "question": "Which element makes up 8.13% of the Earth's crust", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Matsudo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Takagi' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Seychelles is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Saudi Arabia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Qatar", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Iran", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Afghanistan", 
      "Pakistan", 
      "Djibouti", 
      "Somalia", 
      "Turkmenistan", 
      "Iraq", 
      "Eritrea", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Tajikistan", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Jordan"
    ], 
    "question": "Oman shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Copenhagen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Aarhus", 
      "Aalborg", 
      "Roskilde", 
      "Viborg", 
      "Helsinki", 
      "Oslo"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Denmark?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yokohama", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo", 
      "Sendai"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Kawawa?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Cape Verde is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Uzbekistan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tajikistan", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "Pakistan", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Kyrgyzstan", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Georgia", 
      "Iraq", 
      "Oman", 
      "Syria", 
      "Saudi Arabia", 
      "Turkey", 
      "Jordan"
    ], 
    "question": "Turkmenistan shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Brussels", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Antwerp", 
      "Li\u00e8ge", 
      "Amsterdam"
    ], 
    "question": "Where city has the statue, 'Manneken Pis, depicting a naked boy urinating into a fountain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fukushima", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Sasaya' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Dominica?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Slovenia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Croatia", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Albania", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Tunisia", 
      "Germany", 
      "North Macedonia", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Andorra"
    ], 
    "question": "Italy shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pakistan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nepal", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Bhutan"
    ], 
    "question": "Which country in Asia was formerly part of British India? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Vaasa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called V\u00e4h\u00e4kyr\u00f6?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Seychelles?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Colombia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Honduras", 
      "El Salvador", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Belize", 
      "Guatemala", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "Cuba", 
      "Dominican Republic", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Peru", 
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Saint Lucia"
    ], 
    "question": "Panama shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Venezuela", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Canada", 
      "Scotland", 
      "Indonesia"
    ], 
    "question": "____________ possesses more proven oil reserves than any country outside the Middle East.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kawagoe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Kawagoe?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Cape Verde?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "United States of America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nauru", 
      "Marshall Islands", 
      "Kiribati", 
      "Solomon Islands", 
      "Papua New Guinea", 
      "Palau", 
      "Tuvalu", 
      "Vanuatu", 
      "Fiji", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Japan", 
      "East Timor", 
      "Australia", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Brunei", 
      "North Korea", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "New Zealand", 
      "Vietnam"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Federated States of Micronesia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bern", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Geneva", 
      "Zurich", 
      "Basel"
    ], 
    "question": "Which City Is The Capital Of Switzerland?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mito", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Iitomi?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Andorra?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Iran", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tajikistan", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "Pakistan", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Kyrgyzstan", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Georgia", 
      "Iraq", 
      "Oman", 
      "Syria", 
      "Saudi Arabia", 
      "Turkey", 
      "Jordan"
    ], 
    "question": "Turkmenistan shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Riyadh", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mecca", 
      "Medina", 
      "Jeddah"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Saudi Arabia", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Saint Petersburg", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Moscow", 
      "Kazan", 
      "Yekaterinburg", 
      "Ufa", 
      "Rostov-on-Don", 
      "Nizhny Novgorod", 
      "Novosibirsk", 
      "Saratov", 
      "Voronezh", 
      "Perm"
    ], 
    "question": "'Leningrad' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Grenada?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Albania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Montenegro", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Romania", 
      "Malta", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Moldova", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Italy", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Libya", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Austria"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Greece?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Austria and Italy ", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Estonia and Latvia", 
      "Iran and Iraq", 
      "Morocco and Tunisia"
    ], 
    "question": "What two countries do Tyroleans come from? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Raahe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Pattijoki?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Kiribati?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "India", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tajikistan", 
      "Kyrgyzstan", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Turkmenistan", 
      "Oman", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Kazakhstan", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "Maldives", 
      "Myanmar"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Pakistan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Etna", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Vesuvius", 
      "Amiata", 
      "Pico"
    ], 
    "question": "What volcano showers ash on Sicily? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aomori", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Takada' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Bahrain is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "France", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Switzerland", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Italy", 
      "Andorra", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Belgium", 
      "Germany", 
      "Austria", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Kingdom of the Netherlands", 
      "Tunisia", 
      "Malta", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Spain", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Hungary"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Monaco?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Warsaw", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Krakow", 
      "Poznan", 
      "Lodz"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Poland?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cartagena", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madrid", 
      "Barcelona", 
      "Valencia", 
      "Seville", 
      "Bilbao", 
      "Zaragoza", 
      "Reus", 
      "Palma de Mallorca", 
      "Pamplona", 
      "Granada"
    ], 
    "question": "'Qartayannat al-Halfa' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Seychelles is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Canada", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Belize", 
      "Guatemala", 
      "Cuba", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Honduras", 
      "El Salvador", 
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Dominican Republic", 
      "Panama", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Colombia", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "Saint Lucia"
    ], 
    "question": "United States of America shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sudan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Eritrea", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Djibouti", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Chad", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Central African Republic"
    ], 
    "question": "_________ is the largest country in Africa. It has a population greater than 28,100,000.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Cartagena", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madrid", 
      "Barcelona", 
      "Valencia", 
      "Seville", 
      "Bilbao", 
      "Zaragoza", 
      "Reus", 
      "Palma de Mallorca", 
      "Pamplona", 
      "Granada"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Qartayannat al-Halfa?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Saint Kitts and Nevis is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Turkmenistan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pakistan", 
      "Iran", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Oman", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Georgia", 
      "Iraq", 
      "India", 
      "Saudi Arabia", 
      "Bhutan"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Uzbekistan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Water", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Salt", 
      "Foliage", 
      "Human Settlement"
    ], 
    "question": "Over 75% of the Earth's surface is covered by some form of _____.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Aubervilliers", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paris", 
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Lyon", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Toulouse", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called La Chapelle?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Saint Vincent and the Grenadines?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Guatemala", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Honduras", 
      "El Salvador", 
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Cuba", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Panama", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Dominican Republic", 
      "Colombia", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "United States of America", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Grenada"
    ], 
    "question": "Belize shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kuwait City", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Abu Dhabi", 
      "Doha", 
      "Amman"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Kuwait?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kanazawa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Katazu?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kingdom of the Netherlands", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Switzerland", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Denmark", 
      "United Kingdom", 
      "Andorra", 
      "Austria", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Italy", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Ireland", 
      "Spain", 
      "Poland", 
      "Sweden"
    ], 
    "question": "Belgium shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ottawa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Toronto", 
      "Montreal", 
      "Vancouver", 
      "Winnipeg", 
      "Calgary"
    ], 
    "question": "The city name ________________ is derived from an Algonquin word meaning \"traders.\"", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "\u00c4\u00e4nekoski", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "'Suolahti' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Belize is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Russia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bhutan", 
      "North Korea", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Laos", 
      "Kyrgyzstan", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "India", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Tajikistan", 
      "Japan", 
      "Cambodia", 
      "Kazakhstan", 
      "Pakistan", 
      "Uzbekistan", 
      "Philippines"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Mongolia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "El Salvador", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Honduras", 
      "Guatemala", 
      "Belize", 
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Panama", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Cuba"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the smallest of the Central American countries", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Gifu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Miwa' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Togo is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kingdom of the Netherlands", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "United Kingdom", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Ireland", 
      "Austria", 
      "Denmark", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Portugal", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Tunisia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders France?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oakland", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Washington, D.C.", 
      "Los Angeles", 
      "Philadelphia", 
      "Boston", 
      "New Orleans", 
      "San Fransico", 
      "Santa Rosa", 
      "Sacramento", 
      "San Jose", 
      "Reno"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city lies on the east side of San Francisco Bay?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Baden", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Z\u00fcrich", 
      "Bern", 
      "Geneva", 
      "Basel", 
      "Lausanne", 
      "Winterthur", 
      "Lucerne", 
      "St. Gallen", 
      "Lugano", 
      "Fribourg"
    ], 
    "question": "'D\u00e4ttwil' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Monaco is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sudan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Malta", 
      "Greece", 
      "Albania", 
      "North Macedonia", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Italy", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Serbia", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Bulgaria", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Israel", 
      "Slovenia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Libya?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Israel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jordan", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Syria", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Turkey", 
      "Iraq", 
      "Saudi Arabia"
    ], 
    "question": "____________ is one_quarter the size of the state of Maine.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "New York City", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Washington, D.C.", 
      "Los Angeles", 
      "Chicago", 
      "Philadelphia", 
      "San Francisco", 
      "Boston", 
      "New Orleans", 
      "Baltimore", 
      "Seattle", 
      "Indianapolis"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called New Amsterdam?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Nauru is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tanzania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kenya", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Malawi", 
      "Zambia", 
      "Central African Republic", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Angola", 
      "Zimbabwe", 
      "Sudan", 
      "Comoros", 
      "Mozambique", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Djibouti", 
      "Somalia", 
      "Eritrea"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Rwanda?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Brussels", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Antwerp", 
      "Ghent", 
      "Li\u00e8ge", 
      "Bruges", 
      "Leuven", 
      "Mechelen", 
      "Schaerbeek", 
      "Brussels-Capital Region"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Belgium?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yokkaichi", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Tomida?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Tonga is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Laos", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Malaysia", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "People's Republic of China", 
      "India", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Nepal", 
      "East Timor", 
      "Palau", 
      "Maldives", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Mongolia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Cambodia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Reykjavik\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fleykjavik", 
      "Jeykjavik", 
      "Teykjavik"
    ], 
    "question": "Which City Is The Capital Of Iceland? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tongeren", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brussels", 
      "Antwerp", 
      "Ghent", 
      "Li\u00e8ge", 
      "Bruges", 
      "Leuven", 
      "Mechelen", 
      "Schaerbeek", 
      "Brussels-Capital Region", 
      "Anderlecht"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Elderen?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Monaco?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nauru", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tuvalu", 
      "Solomon Islands", 
      "Vanuatu", 
      "Fiji", 
      "Papua New Guinea", 
      "Palau", 
      "Japan", 
      "East Timor", 
      "Philippines", 
      "New Zealand", 
      "Australia", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "North Korea", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Vietnam"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Marshall Islands?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Mount Kilimanjaro", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mount Kenya", 
      "Mount Mawazi", 
      "Mount Ngaliema"
    ], 
    "question": "Name the highest mountain in Africa.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Takasaki", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Nagano?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Monaco is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Bulgaria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Montenegro", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Romania", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Moldova", 
      "Malta", 
      "Italy", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Austria", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Poland", 
      "Ukraine", 
      "Cyprus"
    ], 
    "question": "North Macedonia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Senegal", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Gambia", 
      "Guinea-Bissau", 
      "Guinea", 
      "Sierra Leone", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Liberia", 
      "Cape Verde", 
      "Ivory Coast"
    ], 
    "question": "Dakar is the capital of ______?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio", 
      "Porvoo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Korpilahti?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Monaco is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Albania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Montenegro", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Romania", 
      "Malta", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Moldova", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Italy", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Libya", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Austria"
    ], 
    "question": "Greece shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Vietnam", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cambodia", 
      "Laos", 
      "Thailand", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Philippines"
    ], 
    "question": "In which country is the Mekong River Delta?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Higashi\u014dsaka", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Hiraoka' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Bhutan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Zimbabwe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Burundi", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Eswatini", 
      "South Africa", 
      "Lesotho", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Comoros", 
      "Kenya", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Madagascar", 
      "South Sudan", 
      "Gabon"
    ], 
    "question": "Zambia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Honolulu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hilo", 
      "Kailua", 
      "Maui"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Hawaii?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Rauma", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Lappi?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "South America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Suriname?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Guinea-Bissau", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Gambia", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Togo", 
      "Benin", 
      "Cape Verde", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Algeria", 
      "Niger", 
      "Morocco", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Cameroon"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Guinea?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Luanda", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Brazzaville", 
      "Nairobi", 
      "Dakar"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Angola?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hamamatsu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Iida' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Turkmenistan is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ivory Coast", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Guinea", 
      "Liberia", 
      "Sierra Leone", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "Senegal", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Guinea-Bissau", 
      "The Gambia", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Algeria", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Morocco"
    ], 
    "question": "Burkina Faso shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Equatorial Guinea", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gabon", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "Benin", 
      "Togo", 
      "Central African Republic"
    ], 
    "question": "Malabo is the capital of ______?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Qingdao", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hong Kong", 
      "Beijing", 
      "Shanghai", 
      "Guangzhou", 
      "Chongqing", 
      "Tianjin", 
      "Suzhou", 
      "Nanjing", 
      "Chengdu", 
      "Harbin"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Tsingtao?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Laos is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Slovenia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Croatia", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Albania", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Tunisia", 
      "Germany", 
      "North Macedonia", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Andorra"
    ], 
    "question": "Italy shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Thailand", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cambodia", 
      "Laos", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Malaysia", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Brunei"
    ], 
    "question": "____________ means \"land of the free.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Yverdon-les-Bains", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Z\u00fcrich", 
      "Bern", 
      "Geneva", 
      "Basel", 
      "Lausanne", 
      "Winterthur", 
      "Lucerne", 
      "St. Gallen", 
      "Lugano", 
      "Fribourg"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Gressy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Bahrain is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ivory Coast", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Gambia", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Togo", 
      "Benin", 
      "Cape Verde", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Algeria", 
      "Niger", 
      "Morocco", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Cameroon"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Guinea?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Canada", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "United States of America", 
      "Mexico", 
      "Russia", 
      "China"
    ], 
    "question": "The world's biggest meteor crater is located in which country?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Durr\u00ebs", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tirana", 
      "Shkod\u00ebr", 
      "Kor\u00e7\u00eb", 
      "Vlor\u00eb"
    ], 
    "question": "'Epidamnos' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "South Sudan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Yemen", 
      "Uganda", 
      "Rwanda", 
      "Saudi Arabia", 
      "Tanzania", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Central African Republic", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
      "Seychelles", 
      "Oman", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Egypt"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Ethiopia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Colorado", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mississippi", 
      "Hudson", 
      "Rio Grande"
    ], 
    "question": "Which river made The Grand Canyon?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Paris", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Lyon", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Toulouse", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes", 
      "Rouen"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Seine?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Maldives is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Algeria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Malta", 
      "Italy", 
      "Monaco", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Andorra", 
      "Albania", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Greece", 
      "North Macedonia", 
      "Austria", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Spain", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Tunisia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Belize", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Guatemala", 
      "Honduras", 
      "El Salvador", 
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Panama"
    ], 
    "question": "Which Central American country extends furthest North?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fukui", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Nishiago?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Nauru is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Turkmenistan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan", 
      "Kazakhstan", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Oman", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "India", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Iraq", 
      "Georgia", 
      "Saudi Arabia", 
      "Bhutan"
    ], 
    "question": "Afghanistan shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Pyongyang", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Busan", 
      "Seoul", 
      "Chongjin"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of North Korea?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Hamamatsu", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Iida' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Monaco?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Thailand", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Malaysia", 
      "Singapore", 
      "Brunei", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Philippines", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Indonesia", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "People's Republic of China", 
      "India", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Nepal", 
      "East Timor", 
      "Palau", 
      "Maldives", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Mongolia"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Cambodia?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Israel", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jordan", 
      "Lebanon", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Syria", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Turkey", 
      "Iraq", 
      "Saudi Arabia"
    ], 
    "question": "____________ is one_quarter the size of the state of Maine.", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lugo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Madrid", 
      "Barcelona", 
      "Valencia", 
      "Seville", 
      "Bilbao", 
      "Zaragoza", 
      "Reus", 
      "Palma de Mallorca", 
      "Pamplona", 
      "Granada"
    ], 
    "question": "'Lucus Augusti' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Guinea-Bissau is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Austria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Croatia", 
      "Monaco", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Albania", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Serbia", 
      "Tunisia", 
      "Germany", 
      "North Macedonia", 
      "Luxembourg", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Andorra"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Italy?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Niagara falls", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lake Huron", 
      "Yosemite", 
      "Appalachian Mountains"
    ], 
    "question": "Which site in North America was named after the Mohawk Indian word meaning \"thunder of waters\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Dunkirk", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paris", 
      "Strasbourg", 
      "Lyon", 
      "Nantes", 
      "Marseille", 
      "Toulouse", 
      "Nice", 
      "Montpellier", 
      "Bordeaux", 
      "Rennes"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Rosenda\u00ebl?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Monaco is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Chad", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Togo", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Central African Republic", 
      "Ivory Coast", 
      "Mali", 
      "Liberia", 
      "Guinea", 
      "Democratic Republic of the Congo", 
      "Sierra Leone", 
      "Libya", 
      "Algeria"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Nigeria?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Florida", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Kansas", 
      "Texas", 
      "California"
    ], 
    "question": "Which American state's name is Spanish for \"flowered\" or \"flowery land\"?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio", 
      "Porvoo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Korpilahti' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Nauru is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "United States of America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Nicaragua", 
      "Honduras", 
      "El Salvador", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Jamaica", 
      "Belize", 
      "Guatemala", 
      "Haiti", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "Cuba", 
      "Dominican Republic", 
      "The Bahamas", 
      "Peru", 
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines", 
      "Saint Kitts and Nevis", 
      "Saint Lucia"
    ], 
    "question": "Panama shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Poland", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Slovakia", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Russia"
    ], 
    "question": "Lake Ladoga Is The Largest Lake In Which Country?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Matsuyama", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Wake' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "South America", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Suriname?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Afghanistan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pakistan", 
      "Kazakhstan", 
      "Turkmenistan", 
      "Nepal", 
      "Iran", 
      "India", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "United Arab Emirates", 
      "Oman", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Azerbaijan", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Kuwait", 
      "Armenia", 
      "Georgia", 
      "Iraq"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Tajikistan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Equatorial Guinea", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gabon", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "Benin", 
      "Togo", 
      "Central African Republic"
    ], 
    "question": "Malabo is the capital of ______?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sapporo", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sendai"
    ], 
    "question": "'Toyohira' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Nauru is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Guinea-Bissau", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Gambia", 
      "Burkina Faso", 
      "Ghana", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Togo", 
      "Benin", 
      "Cape Verde", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Algeria", 
      "Niger", 
      "Morocco", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Cameroon"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Guinea?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tripoli", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Benghazi", 
      "Tehran", 
      "Rabat"
    ], 
    "question": "What is the capital of Libya? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Fuch\u016b", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Nishifu' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Indonesia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cambodia", 
      "Vietnam", 
      "Laos", 
      "East Timor", 
      "Myanmar", 
      "Palau", 
      "Sri Lanka", 
      "Bangladesh", 
      "Bhutan", 
      "India", 
      "People's Republic of China", 
      "Maldives", 
      "Nepal", 
      "South Korea", 
      "Papua New Guinea"
    ], 
    "question": "Malaysia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Italy", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Croatia", 
      "Austria", 
      "Switzerland", 
      "Greece", 
      "France"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which Country Is Mount Etna?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Toyonaka", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Sh\u014dnai?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "On which continent would you find the country of Bahrain?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "North Macedonia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Moldova", 
      "Albania", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Hungary", 
      "Slovakia", 
      "Ukraine", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Cyprus", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Belarus", 
      "Poland", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Lithuania", 
      "Austria"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Bulgaria?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Venice\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rome", 
      "Beijing", 
      "Ulaanbaatar"
    ], 
    "question": "In Which City Is Marco Polo Airport?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Kauhava", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Ylih\u00e4rm\u00e4?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Mauritius is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Uganda", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rwanda", 
      "Burundi", 
      "Eritrea", 
      "Djibouti", 
      "Chad", 
      "Tanzania", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Somalia", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Yemen", 
      "Egypt", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Malawi", 
      "Equatorial Guinea"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders South Sudan?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oakland", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Washington, D.C.", 
      "Los Angeles", 
      "Philadelphia", 
      "Boston", 
      "New Orleans", 
      "San Fransico", 
      "Santa Rosa", 
      "Sacramento", 
      "San Jose", 
      "Reno"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city lies on the east side of San Francisco Bay?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Gie\u00dfen", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Berlin", 
      "Munich", 
      "Hamburg", 
      "Leipzig", 
      "Dresden", 
      "Nuremberg", 
      "Hanover", 
      "Stuttgart", 
      "Cologne", 
      "Frankfurt am Main"
    ], 
    "question": "'Lahn' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Oceania", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Federated States of Micronesia is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ukraine", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Czech Republic", 
      "Poland", 
      "North Macedonia", 
      "Albania", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Bulgaria", 
      "Italy", 
      "Greece", 
      "Liechtenstein", 
      "Moldova", 
      "Lithuania", 
      "Germany"
    ], 
    "question": "Which of these countries borders Hungary?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Beijing", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hong Kong", 
      "Shanghai", 
      "Guangzhou", 
      "Nanjing", 
      "Chengdu"
    ], 
    "question": "What Is The Capital Of China?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Shanghai", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hong Kong", 
      "Beijing", 
      "Guangzhou", 
      "Chongqing", 
      "Tianjin", 
      "Suzhou", 
      "Nanjing", 
      "Chengdu", 
      "Harbin", 
      "Wuhan"
    ], 
    "question": "'Shanqhae' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Europe", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Asia", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Liechtenstein is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Austria", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Serbia", 
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina", 
      "Slovenia", 
      "Romania", 
      "Croatia", 
      "Montenegro", 
      "Lithuania", 
      "North Macedonia", 
      "Albania", 
      "Bulgaria", 
      "Moldova", 
      "San Marino", 
      "Belarus", 
      "Latvia", 
      "Italy", 
      "Germany"
    ], 
    "question": "Slovakia shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "San Francisco", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "New York City", 
      "Washington, D.C.", 
      "Los Angeles", 
      "Chicago", 
      "Philadelphia", 
      "Boston", 
      "New Orleans", 
      "Baltimore"
    ], 
    "question": "What city is associated with Alcatraz?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Brunswick", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Berlin", 
      "Munich", 
      "Hamburg", 
      "Leipzig", 
      "Dresden", 
      "Nuremberg", 
      "Hanover", 
      "Stuttgart", 
      "Cologne", 
      "Frankfurt am Main"
    ], 
    "question": "'Braunschweig' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Cape Verde is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Ivory Coast", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Benin", 
      "Nigeria", 
      "Liberia", 
      "Mali", 
      "S\u00e3o Tom\u00e9 and Pr\u00edncipe", 
      "Guinea", 
      "Sierra Leone", 
      "Equatorial Guinea", 
      "Cameroon", 
      "Niger", 
      "Gabon", 
      "Guinea-Bissau", 
      "Senegal", 
      "The Gambia", 
      "Mauritania", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Algeria"
    ], 
    "question": "Ghana shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Washington\u00a0", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Seattle", 
      "New York", 
      "Atlanta"
    ], 
    "question": "In what city is The Smithsonian Institute? ", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Moscow", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Saint Petersburg", 
      "Kazan", 
      "Yekaterinburg", 
      "Ufa", 
      "Rostov-on-Don", 
      "Nizhny Novgorod", 
      "Novosibirsk", 
      "Saratov", 
      "Voronezh", 
      "Perm"
    ], 
    "question": "'Verticali' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Africa", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Asia", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "The country of Lesotho is on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Paraguay", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Peru", 
      "Ecuador", 
      "Suriname", 
      "Colombia", 
      "Guyana", 
      "Venezuela", 
      "Trinidad and Tobago", 
      "Panama", 
      "Grenada", 
      "Saint Vincent and the Grenadines", 
      "Barbados", 
      "Saint Lucia", 
      "Costa Rica", 
      "Dominica", 
      "Antigua and Barbuda"
    ], 
    "question": "Argentina shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Tiber", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rubicon", 
      "Romanus", 
      "Remus"
    ], 
    "question": "Which river runs through Rome?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Lucerne", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Z\u00fcrich", 
      "Bern", 
      "Geneva", 
      "Basel", 
      "Lausanne", 
      "Winterthur", 
      "St. Gallen", 
      "Lugano", 
      "Fribourg", 
      "Neuch\u00e2tel"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Littau?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Maldives is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Sudan", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Burundi", 
      "Ethiopia", 
      "Central African Republic", 
      "Malawi", 
      "Djibouti", 
      "Somalia", 
      "Eritrea", 
      "Zambia", 
      "Republic of the Congo", 
      "Comoros", 
      "Chad", 
      "Angola", 
      "Zimbabwe", 
      "Mozambique"
    ], 
    "question": "Uganda shares a land border with which of these countries?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Colorado", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Arizona", 
      "Utah", 
      "Florida"
    ], 
    "question": "The highest point in Pennsylvania is lower than the lowest point in ______________", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Nagasaki", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tokyo", 
      "\u014csaka", 
      "Kyoto", 
      "Tokyo", 
      "Yokohama", 
      "Kobe", 
      "Nagoya", 
      "Hiroshima", 
      "Fukuoka", 
      "Sapporo"
    ], 
    "question": "Which city used to be called Tomachi?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Venice", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Rome", 
      "Milan", 
      "Naples", 
      "Florence", 
      "Genoa", 
      "Bologna"
    ], 
    "question": "In which city would you find the Bridge of Sighs?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Jyv\u00e4skyl\u00e4", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Helsinki", 
      "Pargas", 
      "Tampere", 
      "Turku", 
      "Oulu", 
      "Pori", 
      "Espoo", 
      "H\u00e4meenlinna", 
      "Kuopio", 
      "Porvoo"
    ], 
    "question": "'Korpilahti' is the old name of which city?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }, 
  {
    "category": "Geography", 
    "correctAnswer": "Asia", 
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "South America", 
      "Oceania", 
      "Europe", 
      "Africa", 
      "North America"
    ], 
    "question": "Kuwait is located on which continent?", 
    "type": "Multiple Choice"
  }
]
